http://www.ncci.org/Pages/PrivacyPolicy.aspx#policy-cookie

Privacy Policy
Posted Date:
Contact Information
About NCCIThe National Council on Compensation Insurance, Inc., (“NCCI”) is a member-funded company organized as a privately held non-stock corporation under the laws of the State of Delaware.
NCCI provides products and services for the workers compensation insurance industry as a licensed rating/advisory organization under the laws of various states, and does not engage in the sale, rental, leasing of, or otherwise provide access to, personal or real property or services to the general public for personal or private use. You can read more about NCCI at our
About Us page.[top]
IntroductionThis NCCI.com Website Privacy Policy explains data collection and use practices of NCCI as they relate to the use of NCCI.com, by our affiliates who are workers compensation insurance carriers and self-insured groups, other workers compensation insurance industry stakeholders and visitors who may access the Website from the United States (collectively, "users"). This privacy policy does not apply to websites, portals, mobile apps, or other online applications that may have their own privacy statement or to any third-party applications that may be made available through NCCI.com, as applicable.
In addition, this Privacy policy does not apply to information collected offline.
NCCI does not sell, share, rent or allow any third party to access and use any information that you have chosen to share with NCCI and/or is collected through your interactions with NCCI.com except as described herein.
NCCI utilizes certain service providers that may be provided certain data or information provided by you or collected through your interactions with NCCI.com and may be stored to facilitate NCCI’s business. Examples of the types of service providers include but are not limited to those providing human capital management systems (applying for a position with NCCI), analytics (deidentified data), shipping and order fulfillment, webinar activities and event registration (event planning, attendee lists, and similar activities).
All service providers have entered into legally binding agreements requiring them to use or disclose such data only as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with applicable legal requirements.
In addition, we may disclose data that may be provided by you or is collected through your interactions with NCCI.com
(a) if we are required or permitted to do so by law or legal process, for example due to a court order or a request from a law enforcement agency, (b) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, (c) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or other illegal activity, and (d) in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation).For purposes of this Website Privacy Policy, “NCCI” means NCCI Holdings, Inc., National Council on Compensation Insurance, Inc., and all subsidiaries.[top]
Information that you provide to usAs a visitor to this site, we do not collect, and you are not required to provide, any personal information, except to the extent it is voluntarily provided by you.
We may collect data or information that you choose to provide to us through NCCI.com including, but not limited to, your first and last name, company name and address, title, mailing/billing address, billing information, e-mail address and telephone number, and other such information such as when you:Sign-up for a product or service that requires an accountSign-up to receive communications from NCCI.comRegister for an event that we have organized such as AIS and State Advisory Forums;Communicate with us via email, or social media platforms.Apply for job or submit a resume to NCCI through our service provider, we will collect any information included in your application or resume, such as name, phone number, resume information, gender, ethnicity, cover letter content, education and field of study, current title and employer, and referring employee (if applicable).Sign into your account[top]
Information Generated Through Your Use of NCCI.comLike most websites and other online services, NCCI.com collects certain information that is created and recorded automatically when you use or interact with NCCI.com. This information includes the following:[top]
Cookie DataWe use the data that we collect automatically through cookies, non-cookie-based tokens, web beacons, and other automated means for purposes such as customizing and enhancing our visitors’ use of NCCI.com, facilitating the performance and use of NCCI.com, collecting statistics about visits to NCCI.com, and understanding the manner in which our users browse NCCI.com. A “cookie” is a small text file that is placed on your system by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can be read only by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Each time you initiate a session on ncci.com, the site sets the cookie in order to identify you and determine your access privileges. Cookies do not store any of the information that you have provided to the site. They are simply identifiers.We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer NCCI.com, and identify account holders visiting NCCI.com. NCCI tracks and catalogs certain information regarding the use of the site, including search terms that you enter, applications used, pages or documents viewed, click stream while on the site, and traffic information. If you are a registered user, this information is stored with your registration information. A unique identification number is used solely for purposes of enabling the site to provide a personalized experience for you. Anonymous or aggregated forms of this data may also be used in order to help us understand areas for future research and to identify future features and functions to develop for the site. This data may also be used to help corporate clients understand how their subscriptions are being used, and to identify appropriate product offerings and subscription plans for them. We use this data for the purposes described above because NCCI has a legitimate interest in operating and improving NCCI.com.
You may have the ability to delete cookie files from your system at any time. However, you should know that cookies may be necessary to provide you with access to much of the content and features of ncci.com. We use cookie technology to enable registered users to move quickly and securely through access-controlled areas of the site. Cookie technology also enables registered users to take advantage of certain useful features on the site, including “remember my password.” We also use third-party web analytic services on NCCI.com such as Google Analytics. The service providers that administer those services may use cookies and web beacons to help us analyze how users use NCCI.com. The information collected by the cookies and web beacons (including your IP address) is available to the service providers, which use the information to evaluate your use of the Site.To learn how to opt out of Google Analytics, visit:
Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on[top]
Log DataWhen you use or interact with the NCCi.com, our servers record certain information that is automatically reported by your browser or device each time you make a request to access NCCI.com or when Website content is downloaded to your browser or device ("log data"). This log data may include your IP address (which may change each time you connect to the Internet—a "dynamic" IP address—or may remain the same—a "static" IP address), browser settings, device information, referring page and URL, the date and time of your request, NCCI.com features or pages viewed, links clicked
and other system performance and cookie data.[top]
Device InformationIn addition to log data, we may collect certain information about the device you're using to access NCCI.com such as the device type, operating system and version, device settings, unique device identifier, advertising identifiers, device motion information, mobile network information, user id, and similar performance data. Whether we collect none, some or all of this device information often depends on what type of device you're using and its settings. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.[top]
Location InformationDepending on the Website features or content and your computer or device permissions, the Website may collect information about your approximate or precise location ("location information"). Various technologies may be used to collect this location information, such as IP address, GPS, and other sensors that may provide information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points, and cell towers.[top]
Transaction DataWhen you request, purchase, or use products and services available through NCCI.com, we collect certain transaction details related to such request, purchase, or use, such as the type of product or service requested, the date and time the product or service was requested and provided, amount charged, purchase and correspondence history, and other related transaction details. If you are using a credit card to purchase a product or service from NCCI.com., NCCI utilizes a third-party payment processor, JP Morgan Chase and Cybersource for such payment. NCCI does not transmit, process, store or maintain any credit card or other payment information. Your interactions with the payment processor are governed by the privacy policies of the payment processor. [top]
Social Media LinksNCCI.com contains certain social media functions, such as links to Twitter, LinkedIn, Facebook and YouTube.
If you use these links, you will leave NCCI.com and will be directed to the linked site.These Social media functions are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with the social media functions located on NCCI.com are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them. If you use any of the social media functions through NCCI.com, you should review their privacy policies. [top]
How We Use the Information That We ObtainWe may use
data or information that you provide to us to respond to your inquiries, for example, to contact you about your request, ask a question, provide announcements about products and future events, conduct surveys, consider your application for employment, and contact you for other reasons related to offerings and improving our services. We use this data and information for these purposes because we have a legitimate business interest in providing services to our users and other interested individuals that is not overridden by your interests, rights and freedoms to protect personal data about you.In addition to the uses discussed above, we may also use the data or information you provide to us or is collected through your use of the website for, without
limitation:Fulfilling product and service orders through the account that
you have set upProviding newsletters, alerts, and informational materials about products, services, news and eventsIdentifying potential products and offerings that may be of
interestDeveloping future content and other NCCI products and services
based on usage tracking data, users’ interests, and our assessment of important
trends and issues in information technology and e-commercePlanning future events Operating, evaluating, and improving our business;Performing market research;Advertising and marketing our products and services;Determining the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing;Analyzing our products, services, and website usability and usage;Administration of NCCI.com.We may also use the information to protect against and prevent fraud, claims, and other liabilities and to comply with or enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, and our policies and terms. We use data for these purposes when it is necessary to protect, exercise or defend our legal rights, or when we are required to do so by law that applies to us.[top]
Third Party WebsitesOccasionally, NCCI provides, as a convenience feature certain links to third party websites not owned or controlled by NCCI. These websites have their own unique legal terms of use, security features and privacy policies which should be reviewed in detail should you desire to access and use such sites. Your use of such third-party sites is not governed by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, NCCI is not responsible for and shall not incur any liability in any way for any content, products or services that are contained or provided on or through any third-party website.[top]
SurveysFrom time to time, we may ask for visitors and account holders to participate in a survey on a voluntary basis. Information requested may include contact
information (e.g., name and shipping address) and demographic information (e.g., zip code). Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, and for internal research purposes. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed to or shared with third parties.[top]
SecurityNCCI provides a secure online experience for users who access NCCI.com. To do this, we use a variety of security measures to maintain the safety and confidentiality of your information. All user registration information is contained behind a firewall and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to our production systems. Confidential personal information sent to us is transmitted using industry standard, best practice encryption technologies such as Transport Layer Security and Secure Shell. This information is then encrypted in our secure database. The database is further protected behind a firewall.[top]
How Long We Keep InformationThe time period for which we keep data or information you provide to us or is collected through your use of the website depends on the purpose for which it
was provided or collected. In all cases we keep it for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was provided or collected. We will then delete the data or information, unless we are legally required to retain it order to comply with our legal obligations (for example, for tax and accounting purposes).Subject to any applicable legal requirements, we typically retain data as follows: Data you provide to us through our Site: we keep this data for as long as necessary in order to respond to your request, and for a short further period in case you send us further requests. Data collected for analytics purposes: we keep this data for a period of time to carry out the analytics with such information being deidentified. Website logs: we keep Site audit logs, which may contain your data, for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected.[top]
Privacy of ChildrenThis website and privacy policy are not intended for use by children. We understand the importance of protecting the privacy and information of children and do not knowingly collect or maintain information about children.[top]
Changes to this PolicyWe may occasionally update this privacy policy without notice to you. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the information we collect. Your continued use of this Web site constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates to it.[top]
Contact InformationIf you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy please direct them, via e-mail, to our webmaster.[top]
NCCI
Home
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
Website SLA
QUICK LINKS
Events and Programs
Learning Center
Online Invoice Service (OIS)
Services & Tools Catalog
Solutions
LEGAL
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
CONNECT WITH US
We use cookies on this site to enhance your user experience. By continuing to use this site you are giving us your consent to place cookies on your device.
Continue
Give me more information
